{
  "animals": [
    {
      "Question": "Nacktschnecke Is The German Word For Slug, Literally Meaning",
      "Answer": "Naked Snail",
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Raven, A Poem By Edgar Allan Poe, Was Originally Going To Be About",
      "Answer": "A Talking Parrot",
    },
    {
      "Question": "A Baby Echidna Is Called",
      "Answer": "A Puggle",
    },
    {
      "Question": "A Baby Oyster Is Called",
      "Answer": "A Spat",
    },
    {
      "Question": "A Baby Porcupine Is Called",
      "Answer": "A Porcupette",
    },
    {
      "Question": "A Baby Pterosaur Is Called",
      "Answer": "A Flapling",
    },
    {
      "Question": "A Cockroach Can Live Up To 9 Days If It Loses Its Head, Because",
      "Answer": "Its Brain Is In Its Body",
    },
    {
      "Question": "A Female Mouse Is Called",
      "Answer": "A Doe",
    },
    {
      "Question": "A Female Walrus Is Called",
      "Answer": "A Cow",
    },
    {
      "Question": "A Gaze Or A Mask Is A Group Of",
      "Answer": "Raccoons",
    },
    {
      "Question": "A Goat’s Pupil Is",
      "Answer": "Rectangular",
    },
    {
      "Question": "A Group Of Apes Is Called",
      "Answer": "A Shrewdness",
    },
    {
      "Question": "A Group Of Elk Is Called",
      "Answer": "A Gang",
    },
    {
      "Question": "A Group Of Falcons Is Called",
      "Answer": "A Charm",
    },
    {
      "Question": "A Group Of Ferrets Is Called",
      "Answer": "A Business",
    },
    {
      "Question": "A Group Of Geese In The Sky Is Called",
      "Answer": "A Skein",
    },
    {
      "Question": "A Group Of Geese On The Ground Is Called",
      "Answer": "A Gaggle",
    },
    {
      "Question": "A Group Of Hippos Is Called",
      "Answer": "A Bloat",
    },
    {
      "Question": "A Group Of Jellyfish Is Called",
      "Answer": "A Smack",
    },
    {
      "Question": "A Group Of Kangaroos Is Called",
      "Answer": "A Troop",
    },
    {
      "Question": "A Group Of Kittens Is Called",
      "Answer": "An Intrigue",
    },
    {
      "Question": "A Group Of Leopards Is Called",
      "Answer": "A Leap",
    },
    {
      "Question": "A Group Of Moles Is Called",
      "Answer": "A Labor",
    },
    {
      "Question": "A Group Of Otters Is Called",
      "Answer": "A Romp",
    },
    {
      "Question": "A Group Of Peacocks Is Called",
      "Answer": "An Ostentation",
    },
    {
      "Question": "A Group Of Porcupines Is Called",
      "Answer": "A Prickle",
    },
    {
      "Question": "A Group Of Rattlesnakes Is Called",
      "Answer": "A Rhumba",
    },
    {
      "Question": "A Group Of Salamanders Is Called",
      "Answer": "A Congress",
    },
    {
      "Question": "A Group Of Seabirds Is Called",
      "Answer": "A Wreck",
    },
    {
      "Question": "A Group Of Seagulls Is Called",
      "Answer": "A Squabble",
    },
    {
      "Question": "A Group Of Squirrels Is Called",
      "Answer": "A Scurry",
    },
    {
      "Question": "A Group Of Stingrays Is Called",
      "Answer": "A Fever",
    },
    {
      "Question": "A Group Of Swans Is Called",
      "Answer": "A Ballet",
    },
    {
      "Question": "A Group Of Tigers Is Called",
      "Answer": "A Streak",
    },
    {
      "Question": "A Group Of Zebras Is Called",
      "Answer": "A Dazzle",
    },
    {
      "Question": "A Male Guinea Pig Is Called",
      "Answer": "A Boar",
    },
    {
      "Question": "A Male Hippo Attracts A Female By",
      "Answer": "Spraying Her With Excrement",
    },
    {
      "Question": "A Male Panda Marks His Territory By",
      "Answer": "Doing A Handstand And Urinating As High As He Can On A Tree",
    },
    {
      "Question": "A Male Woodchuck Is Called",
      "Answer": "A He-chuck",
    },
    {
      "Question": "A Pig Will Have A Larger Litter If She",
      "Answer": "Is Petted",
    },
    {
      "Question": "A Porpoise Does This When Searching For A Mate",
      "Answer": "Swims Upside Down",
    },
    {
      "Question": "A Praying Mantis Has One Ear Located",
      "Answer": "Between Its Legs",
    },
    {
      "Question": "A Raccoon Appears To Do This To Food Before Eating It",
      "Answer": "Wash It",
    },
    {
      "Question": "A Sea Hare Secretes A Purple Slime That Does This To Predators",
      "Answer": "Blocks Their Noses So They Don’t Realize How Delicious The Sea Hare Smells",
    },
    {
      "Question": "A Skulk Is A Group Of",
      "Answer": "Foxes",
    },
    {
      "Question": "A Stubbornness Is A Group Of",
      "Answer": "Rhinoceroses",
    },
    {
      "Question": "A Velvet Ant Is A Type Of",
      "Answer": "Wasp",
    },
    {
      "Question": "According To Wait! Wait! Don’t Tell Me, Scientists In France Have Determined That Lizards Have",
      "Answer": "Personalities",
    },
    {
      "Question": "According To Government Studies, It’s Possible For Pigs To Become",
      "Answer": "Alchoholics",
    },
    {
      "Question": "According To The Game Manual For The Original Donkey Kong, Mario Was The Villain Because",
      "Answer": "He Abused His Giant Pet Ape Who Got Fed Up And Escaped",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Adult Burying Beetles Will Punish Their Offspring Who Nag For Food By",
      "Answer": "Eating Them",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Alligators Do This To Lure Nest-Building Birds",
      "Answer": "Put Twigs On Their Snouts",
    },
    {
      "Question": "An Aboistop Is A Device That",
      "Answer": "Sprays A Distracting Scent In Front Of Your Dogs When He Barks",
    },
    {
      "Question": "An Ant Will Always Fall Over To Its Right Side When",
      "Answer": "Intoxicated",
    },
    {
      "Question": "An Illegal Exporter Of Sheep Is Called",
      "Answer": "An Owler",
    },
    {
      "Question": "An Orangutan Named Sandra In The Buenos Aires Zoo Is The First",
      "Answer": "Non-human To Be Recognized As A Person In A Court Of Law",
    },
    {
      "Question": "An Unkindness Or Storytelling Is A Group Of",
      "Answer": "Ravens",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Andrew Jackson’s Parrot Did This At His Funeral",
      "Answer": "Shouted Obscenities",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Ants Do This As They Pass One Another",
      "Answer": "Nod",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Ants Have Five",
      "Answer": "Noses",
    },
    {
      "Question": "As Soon As Tiger Shark Embryos Develop Teeth, They Do This In The Womb",
      "Answer": "Attack And Even Eat One Another",
    },
    {
      "Question": "At The Cockroach Museum In Texas, You Can Find Liberoachi And David Letteroach, Which Are",
      "Answer": "Dead Cockroaches Dressed As Celebrities",
    },
    {
      "Question": "At The Vancouver Aquarium, Vets Helped Stop The Bullying Of A One-Eyed Yellowtail Rockfish By",
      "Answer": "Giving It A Fake Eye",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Baby Hedgehogs Are Called",
      "Answer": "Hoglets",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Baby Puffins Are Called",
      "Answer": "Pufflings",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Baby Seals Are Called",
      "Answer": "Weaners",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Baby Squirrels Are Called",
      "Answer": "Kittens",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Because Of The Accidents They Cause Each Year, This Is Technically The Most Dangerous Mammal In North America",
      "Answer": "The White-tailed Deer",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Before It Sprays, The Eastern Spotted Skunk",
      "Answer": "Does A Handstand",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Beneath Its Fur, A Skunk’s Skin Is",
      "Answer": "Striped",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Chimps In West Africa Are Known To Use Leaves As Sponges To",
      "Answer": "Soak Up Fermenting Sap And Get Drunk",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Cows Are Sometimes Put In A Bra In Order To",
      "Answer": "Prevent Them From Stepping On Their Own Udders",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Cows Become Distressed If They’re Separated From",
      "Answer": "Their Best Friends",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Crows Enjoy Doing This For Fun",
      "Answer": "Pranking One Another",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Deathwatch Beetles Attract Mates By",
      "Answer": "Repeatedly Banging Their Heads On The Floor",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Due To The Film’s Happy Ending, Garfield’s Favorite Movie Is",
      "Answer": "Old Yeller",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Dung Beetles Navigate By Using",
      "Answer": "The Milky Way",
    },
    {
      "Question": "During Courtship, Male Birds In Australia Have Been Heard Mimicking This Sound",
      "Answer": "A Cell Phone Ringing",
    },
    {
      "Question": "During Wwii, The Us Government Considered Using Domesticated Birds To Guide Bombs, In An Operation Dubbed",
      "Answer": "Project Pigeon",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Fifty-Five Million Years Ago, Whales Could",
      "Answer": "Walk",
    },
    {
      "Question": "From 1.8 Miles Away, A Male Gypsy Moth Can Smell",
      "Answer": "A Virgin Female Gypsy Moth",
    },
    {
      "Question": "From The Pavement Of Broadway, New York, Ants Eat The Equivalent Of 60,000",
      "Answer": "Hotdogs",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Goldfish Remember Better When",
      "Answer": "They’re In Cold Water",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Hamsters Blink By",
      "Answer": "Closing One Eye At A Time",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Hawaii’s State Fish Is The",
      "Answer": "Humuhumunukunukuapua’a",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Henry Ibsen Kept This Pet In An Empty Beer Glass On His Desk For Inspiration",
      "Answer": "A Scorpion",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Henry Iii Kept Four Of These In The Tower Of London",
      "Answer": "Lions",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Herring Communicate By",
      "Answer": "Firing Bubbles From Their Butts",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Hippopotamus Bites Are Almost Always Fatal Because",
      "Answer": "They’re Very Large",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Hippos Cannot",
      "Answer": "Swim",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Honey Bees Communicate By",
      "Answer": "Dancing",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Humans And Horses Are The Only Animals That Have",
      "Answer": "Hymens",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Humpback Whales Can Do This Non-Stop For 20 Hours",
      "Answer": "Sing",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Humpback Whales, Elephants, Some Monkeys, And Humans Are The Only Mammals That Experience",
      "Answer": "Menopause",
    },
    {
      "Question": "If A Baby Kangaroo Is Scared, They Will",
      "Answer": "Dive Headfirst Into Their Mother’s Pouch",
    },
    {
      "Question": "If A Cockroach Touches A Person, It Immediately Runs Away And",
      "Answer": "Washes Itself",
    },
    {
      "Question": "If A Deer Becomes Dehydrated, Its Urine",
      "Answer": "Might Turn Blue",
    },
    {
      "Question": "If You Feed A Wild Moose Often Enough, It Will",
      "Answer": "Attack People Who Don’t Feed It",
    },
    {
      "Question": "If You Give Prozac To A Snail,",
      "Answer": "It Can No Longer Stick To Surfaces",
    },
    {
      "Question": "In 1252 King Henry Iii Was Gifted A Pet",
      "Answer": "Polar Bear",
    },
    {
      "Question": "In 1255, King Henry Iii Was Gifted",
      "Answer": "An Elephant",
    },
    {
      "Question": "In 1494 A Pig Was Once Tried In Court For",
      "Answer": "Murder",
    },
    {
      "Question": "In 2008, These Animals Were Banned As Pets In Vietnam",
      "Answer": "Hamsters",
    },
    {
      "Question": "In 2009, Google’s Mountain View Headquarters Hired A Team Of 200 Goats To",
      "Answer": "Mow Their Overgrown Fields",
    },
    {
      "Question": "In Case The First One Breaks Off, The European Earwig Has A Spare",
      "Answer": "Penis",
    },
    {
      "Question": "In Order To Attract Mates, Jumping Spiders Are Known To Do A Move That Mimics",
      "Answer": "Breakdancing",
    },
    {
      "Question": "In The 1970S, Stories Took The Nation By Storm Of A Humanzee –A Half Human, Half Chimp Named",
      "Answer": "Oliver",
    },
    {
      "Question": "It Has Been Said That Female Baboons Engage In A Primitive Form Of Prostitution By",
      "Answer": "Stealing Food During Sex",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Japanese Yellow Swallowtail Butterflies Can See With",
      "Answer": "Their Eyes And Bottoms",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Kangaroos Have Three Of These",
      "Answer": "Vaginas",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Karl Lagerfeld’s Cat Has",
      "Answer": "Two Maids",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Koalas Don’t Need To Do This",
      "Answer": "Drink",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Koshima Island Monkeys And Humans Are The Only Creatures That Intentionally Do This",
      "Answer": "Salt Their Food",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Leeches Have 18",
      "Answer": "Testicles",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Lord Byron Had Four Of These As Pets That He Took Everywhere With Him",
      "Answer": "Geese",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Macaques Make These For Entertainment",
      "Answer": "Snowballs",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Male Eland Antelopes Let Other Males Know How Tough They Are By",
      "Answer": "Clicking Their Knees",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Male Fruitflies That Have Been Rejected By Females Are Known To Do This More Than Those Who Haven’t",
      "Answer": "Drink Alcohol",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Male Mosquitos Eat",
      "Answer": "Sap",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Marcel Proust Kept A Pet",
      "Answer": "Swordfish",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Mares Have A Preference For Stallions With This Trait",
      "Answer": "Deep Voices",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Marine Turtles Rid Their Bodies Of Excess Salt By",
      "Answer": "Weeping",
    },
    {
      "Question": "More Than Any Other Ailment, This Kills The Most Fruit Flies",
      "Answer": "Constipation",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Mosquitos Have 47",
      "Answer": "Teeth",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Most Kangaroos Are",
      "Answer": "Left-handed",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Northern Leopard Frogs Swallow Their Prey Using",
      "Answer": "Their Eyes",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Observed Copulating Over 200 Times In Two Hours With The Same Mate Is A Desert Rat Called",
      "Answer": "The Shaw’s Jird",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Olive Sea Snakes Have Photoreceptors In Their Tails So That",
      "Answer": "They Know Whether Or Not They’re Sticking Out When They’re Hiding",
    },
    {
      "Question": "On August 20, 1949, The Big Ben Ran Four Minutes Slow Because",
      "Answer": "Hundreds Of Birds Were Sitting On Its Hands",
    },
    {
      "Question": "On Labor Day Each Year, Contenstants In The Wisconsin State Chip Throw Compete To See Who Can",
      "Answer": "Throw A Cow Poop Patty The Farthest",
    },
    {
      "Question": "One Hundred Athletes Taking Part In The Scottish Triathlon In 2005 Were Insured Against",
      "Answer": "Being Bitten By The Loch Ness Monster",
    },
    {
      "Question": "One Thousand Years After The Egyptians Finished Building The Great Pyramid, This Animal Went Extinct",
      "Answer": "The Mammoth",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Otters Can Get This Human Disease",
      "Answer": "Herpes",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Oysters Change This Up To Four Times A Year",
      "Answer": "Their Sex",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Parrots Give Each Of Their Offspring",
      "Answer": "Unique Names",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Pigeons Don’t Bob Their Heads While Walking If",
      "Answer": "They Are Walking On A Treadmill",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Pigeons Never Forget",
      "Answer": "A Face",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Praire Dogs Greet One Another With",
      "Answer": "Kisses",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Pregnant Goldfish Are Known As",
      "Answer": "Twits",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Ravens Have Been Known To Do This To Drug Themselves",
      "Answer": "Sit On An Ant Hill And Let The Ants Bite Them",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Red Pandas Use Their Bushy Tails As",
      "Answer": "Blankets To Help Stay Warm",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Scotland’s National Animal Is",
      "Answer": "The Unicorn",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Sea Otters Have A Pouch Under Their Forearm That They Use To",
      "Answer": "Store Food And Their Favorite Rocks",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Sheep Can Recognize And Are Very Fond Of A Human With",
      "Answer": "A Smile",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Snake Scales Are Made Of The Same Material As",
      "Answer": "Human Fingernails",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Some People Think That The Albino Or White Deer Is",
      "Answer": "A Modern Day Unicorn With Magical Powers",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Some Pigs Suffer From Mysophobia, Which Is The Fear Of",
      "Answer": "Mud",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Spiders Have 48 Of These",
      "Answer": "Knees",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Squid Do This Almost Always At Night",
      "Answer": "Fly",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Squirrels Are Immune To",
      "Answer": "Rabies",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Swans Are The Only Birds That Have",
      "Answer": "Penises",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Ted Turner Owns 50,000",
      "Answer": "Bison",
    },
    {
      "Question": "The African Giant Pouched Rat Can Smell This 50 Times Faster Than A Scientist Can Identify It",
      "Answer": "Tuberculosis",
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Animal Responsible For The Most Human Deaths Worldwide Is",
      "Answer": "The Mosquito",
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Camouflaged Spider-Tailed Horned Viper Attracts Its Prey With",
      "Answer": "A Fake Spider On The End Of Its Tail",
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Cheetah Is The Only Member Of The Cat Family That Cannot",
      "Answer": "Retract Its Claws",
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Cigarette Snail Received Its Name Because",
      "Answer": "If It Bites Someone, They Have Just Enough Time To Smoke A Cigarette Before Dying",
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Common Shrew Protects Itself From Predators By",
      "Answer": "Dying Of Fright",
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Cornish Name For A Bat Is",
      "Answer": "An Airymouse",
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Cougar, Or Mountain Lion, Holds The Guinness World Record For",
      "Answer": "The Animal With The Most Names",
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Current Record For The Longest Mating Session Of This Animal Is 22.75 Hours",
      "Answer": "The Rattlesnake",
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Defensive Coach Of The Minnesota Vikings Had His Defensive Lineman Prepare For Runningback Barry Sanders By",
      "Answer": "Chasing Chickens",
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Foot Of A Scaly-Foot Snail Is Covered With",
      "Answer": "Iron Armour Plating",
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Heathrow Airport Has Cars With Loudspeakers Playing",
      "Answer": "The Distress Calls Of Birds To Keep Them Away From The Runway",
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Horn Of A Rhinoceros Is Made From",
      "Answer": "Compacted Hair",
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Jamaican Fruit Bat Smells Like",
      "Answer": "Soap",
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Largest Millipede In Tanzania Is Called",
      "Answer": "The Wandering Leg Sausage",
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Mallee Bird Of Australia Can Do This With His Tongue",
      "Answer": "Tell The Temperature",
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Montane Emo Skink, The Bicolored Foxface, And The Twilight Fangblenny Are Animals Found In",
      "Answer": "Fiji",
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Moth Called The Beautiful Wood Nymph Has Evolved To Look Like",
      "Answer": "Bird Poo",
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Mouse-Sized Rodent That Can Jump Up To Ten Feet In The Air Is Called The",
      "Answer": "Jerboa",
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Name Jaguar Comes From A Native American Word Meaning",
      "Answer": "He Who Kills With One Leap",
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Name Of A Suckling Calf Is",
      "Answer": "A Bob",
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Name Of The Only Bird Known To Hibernate In North America Is The",
      "Answer": "North American Whippoorwill",
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Only Hard Part Of An Octopus Body Is",
      "Answer": "Its Beak",
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Part Of A Snail That’s Inside Of The Shell Is Called",
      "Answer": "A Mantle",
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Real Name Of Batman’s Adversary The Penguin Is",
      "Answer": "Oswald Cobblepot",
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Sami People Refer To A Polar Bear As",
      "Answer": "The Old Man In The Fur Coat",
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Scaptia Beyonceae Is A Horsefly Named For",
      "Answer": "Its Large Rear End",
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Sword-Billed Hummingbird Is The Only Bird That",
      "Answer": "Has A Bill Longer Than Its Body",
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Tarsier Is The Only Primate That’s Known To Communicate By",
      "Answer": "Ultrasound",
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Turritopsis Nutricula, A Species Of Jellyfish, Is Known For Being",
      "Answer": "Immortal",
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Word Struthious Means",
      "Answer": "Resembling An Ostrich",
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Word For Hamster In Arabic Translates As",
      "Answer": "Mr. Saddlebags",
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Word For Otter Poop Is",
      "Answer": "Spraint",
    },
    {
      "Question": "The World’s Smallest Breed Of Horse Is The",
      "Answer": "Falabella",
    },
    {
      "Question": "There Is A Group Of Chimps In Zambia Who Have Started Doing This For Ornamentation",
      "Answer": "Wearing Blades Of Grass In Their Ears",
    },
    {
      "Question": "This Animal’s Milk Is Twice As Thick As Whipping Cream",
      "Answer": "Elephant Seal",
    },
    {
      "Question": "This Celebrity Was A Huge Animal Lover And Had Pets Including Ducks, Fish, Peacocks, A Parrot, And A Chimpanzee",
      "Answer": "Elvis",
    },
    {
      "Question": "This Creature Carries Sea Anemones In Its Claws To Wave Around When Threatened",
      "Answer": "The Pom Pom Crab",
    },
    {
      "Question": "This Creature Was Stowed Away On The Apollo Xii Flight",
      "Answer": "The Cockroach",
    },
    {
      "Question": "This Happens To A Tasmanian Devil If You Make Them Angry",
      "Answer": "Their Ears Turn Red",
    },
    {
      "Question": "This Is A Unique Feature Of Hippo Milk",
      "Answer": "It’s Bright Pink",
    },
    {
      "Question": "This Is A Unique Feature Of Wombat Poop",
      "Answer": "It’s Cube-shaped",
    },
    {
      "Question": "This Is The Word In Afrikaans For An Elephant’s Trunk",
      "Answer": "Slurp",
    },
    {
      "Question": "This Male Mammal Has The Highest Rate Of Homosexuality",
      "Answer": "The Bat",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Tigers Are Known To Do This To Lure Prey",
      "Answer": "Immitate The Sounds Of Other Animals",
    },
    {
      "Question": "To Control Cockroaches, The Victorians Kept These In Their Kitchens",
      "Answer": "Hedgehogs",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Tomato Frogs Produce A Glue That",
      "Answer": "Causes A Predator’s Lips To Stick Together",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Until The 20Th Century, Bumblebees Were Called",
      "Answer": "Humblebees",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Water Droplets Bouncing Off A Gecko’s Skin Are Called",
      "Answer": "Geckovescence",
    },
    {
      "Question": "When A Female Rhinoceros Is In The Mood, She Does This To Her Lover",
      "Answer": "Rams Him With Her Horns",
    },
    {
      "Question": "When A Horse Is Excited He Makes A Noise Called A",
      "Answer": "Nicker",
    },
    {
      "Question": "When Attacking, Bull Sharks Have Been Known To Do This To Continue Pursuing Their Victim",
      "Answer": "Follow Them Onto Land",
    },
    {
      "Question": "When Guinea Pigs Hop And Leap From Excitement, It’s Called",
      "Answer": "Popcorning",
    },
    {
      "Question": "When Hermit Crabs Find A New Shell, They",
      "Answer": "Line Up From Biggest To Smallest To Pass On The Shells They’ve Outgrown",
    },
    {
      "Question": "When Introduced To Different Groups, Goats Will Change",
      "Answer": "Their Way Of Speaking",
    },
    {
      "Question": "When Rabbits Jump And Twist Out Of Excitement, It Is Called",
      "Answer": "A Binky",
    },
    {
      "Question": "When Robins Eat Holly Berries They",
      "Answer": "Get Drunk",
    },
    {
      "Question": "White-Faced Capuchin Monkeys Do This When Greeting One Another",
      "Answer": "Stick Their Fingers Up One Another’s Noses",
    },
    {
      "Question": "Worms Get Addicted To This",
      "Answer": "Nicotine",
    },
    {
      "Question": "You Can Find These On The Tail Of A Horseshoe Crab",
      "Answer": "Eyes",
    },
    {
      "Question": "You Can Tell The Age Of A Whale By",
      "Answer": "Counting The Rings In Its Earwax",
    }
  ]
}